Civil Service Employees Association, Inc. (CSEA), American Federation of State, County, and Municipal Employees (AFSCME) Local 1000 Records apap015
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- Images, 1947-2013; 10; 2.8 cubic ft.
  - Civil Service Employees Association (CSEA)..., 2001 September
  - A plaque inscribed with the names of 39 state..., 2001 September
  - Civil Service Employees Association (CSEA)..., 2005 September
  - Just days before the fifth anniversary of the..., 2006 September
  - Civil Service Employees Association (CSEA)..., 2006 September
  - Unidentified Civil Service Employees Association..., 2006 September
  - Civil Service Employees Association (CSEA) member..., 2006 September
  - Civil Service Employees Association (CSEA)'s..., 2007 September
  - Unidentifed Civil Service Employees Association..., 2007 September
  - A distant photo of the World Trade Center towers..., 2001 September 11
  - Delegates to the Civil Service Employees..., 2002 September 11
  - The devastation at Ground Zero following the..., 2001 September 21
- Scrapbooks, 1958-1971; 11; 2.70 cubic ft.
  This series is composed of scrapbooks from the Oneida County CSEA Chapter and secretary of Local 767, Dorothy Dutton. The scrapbooks generally include news clippings, photographs, flyers, notices, etc. Photographs were removed from scrapbooks 2, 3, and 4 for preservation reasons.
  - Scrabook 1, 1958-1979 (Oversized 28)
  - Scrabook 2, 1960-1966 (Oversized 28)
  - Scrabook 3, 1967-1968 (Oversized 29)
  - Scrabook 4, 1968-1969 (Oversized 29)
  - Scrabook 5, 1969-1971 (Oversized 30)
  - Scrabook 6, 1972-1976 (Oversized 30)
  - Scrabook 7, 1980-1983 (Oversized 31)
  - Scrabook 8, 1980-1986 (Oversized 31)
  - Scrabook 9, 1981-1994 (Oversized 32)
  - Scrabook 10, 1990-1994 (Oversized 33)
  - Scrabook 11, 1967-1971 (Oversized 34)
- Membership, 1939-2015; 12; 2.6 cubic ft.
  The membership series contains materials produced by CSEA headquarters for its members. It contains resource manuals on a variety of subjects such as test preparation for the civil service exams, how to submit an amendment or proposal to the statewide constitution, and educational assistance. Materials about each of the five regions are included as well as materials pertaining to the internal departments at headquarters. In addition, there are a number of pamphlets aimed at members along with flyers about the benefits of being a member in the union.
  - AFCSME Election of Delegates, 2010 (Box 1 (12-Membership), Folder 1)
  - Advertising Kit for Locals from Headquarters, 1978 October 16 (Box 1 (12-Membership), Folder 2)
  - Budget Alert: Call your local Assemblyperson Senator and Governer, 1997 January 15 (Box 1 (12-Membership), Folder 3)
  - Basic Guide for Treasurers, Undated (Box 1 (12-Membership), Folder 4)
  - Budget Memo, Undated (Box 1 (12-Membership), Folder 5)
  - Budget Proposals and Summaries (1 of 6), 2010-2015; Undated (Box 1 (12-Membership), Folder 6)
  - Budget Proposals and Summaries (2 of 6), 2010-2015; Undated (Box 1 (12-Membership), Folder 7)
  - Budget Proposals and Summaries (3 of 6), 2010-2015; Undated (Box 1 (12-Membership), Folder 8)
  - Budget Proposals and Summaries (4 of 6), 2010-2015; Undated (Box 1 (12-Membership), Folder 9)
  - Budget Proposals and Summaries (5 of 6), 2010-2015; Undated (Box 1 (12-Membership), Folder 10)
  - Budget Proposals and Summaries (6 of 6), 2010-2015; Undated (Box 1 (12-Membership), Folder 11)
  - Budget Reports by Account/Program, 2006-2009 (Box 1 (12-Membership), Folder 12)
  - Committees, 1988-1989 (Box 1 (12-Membership), Folder 13)
  - Organizing for Change, Changing to Organize, Undated (Box 1 (12-Membership), Folder 14)
  - CSEA Alert: The President's Plan and the Survival of the Working Class, Undated (Box 1 (12-Membership), Folder 15)
  - CSEA Membership Phamplets, Undated (Box 1 (12-Membership), Folder 16)
  - CSEA's VOICE (Voice of Independent Child-Care Educators), 2008-2009; Undated (Box 1 (12-Membership), Folder 17)
  - Cliff Merritt, Comics about Labor Unions from UTO, Undated (Box 1 (12-Membership), Folder 18)
  - CBTU National Convention in Phoenix, AZ, 2005 May 28 (Box 1 (12-Membership), Folder 19)
  - Direct-Dial Phone List, Undated (Box 1 (12-Membership), Folder 20)
  - Educational Assistance Program, 2013-2014 (Box 1 (12-Membership), Folder 21)
  - Education and Training Department Membership Materials, 1996; 2002; 2005; Undated (Box 1 (12-Membership), Folder 22)
  - Election Ballot for the 2000 Statewide contract (Box 1 (12-Membership), Folder 23)
  - Election Materials (1 of 2), 2010; 2013; Undated (Box 1 (12-Membership), Folder 24)
  - Election Materials (2 of 2), 2010; 2013; Undated (Box 1 (12-Membership), Folder 25)
  - Employee Benefits, 2012 (Box 1 (12-Membership), Folder 26)
  - Employee Benefits Training Courses, 1982 August (Box 1 (12-Membership), Folder 27)
  - Grievance Representation Workshop, Undated (Box 1 (12-Membership), Folder 28)
  - Honoring Diversity, Undated (Box 1 (12-Membership), Folder 29)
  - Insurance Department Death Claims (1 of 6), 1988 (Box 1 (12-Membership), Folder 30)
  - Insurance Department Death Claims (2 of 6), 1988 (Box 1 (12-Membership), Folder 31)
  - Insurance Department Death Claims (3 of 6), 1988 (Box 1 (12-Membership), Folder 32)
  - Insurance Department Death Claims (4 of 6), 1988 (Box 1 (12-Membership), Folder 33)
  - Insurance Department Death Claims (5 of 6), 1988 (Box 1 (12-Membership), Folder 34)
  - Insurance Department Death Claims (6 of 6), 1988 (Box 1 (12-Membership), Folder 35)
  - Insurance Department Death Claims Paid (Book), 1939 June- 1961 January (Oversized 35)
  - Insurance Department Death Claims Paid (Book), 1962 January-1970 March 17 (Oversized 35)
  - Insurance Department Death Claims Paid (Book), 1970 February 1-1973 March 15 (Oversized 36)
  - Insurance Department Death Claims Paid (Book), 1973-1987 (Oversized 36)
  - Insurance Department Death Claims - Processed (1 of 6), 1989 August-2004 May (Box 1 (12-Membership), Folder 36)
  - Insurance Department Death Claims - Processed (2 of 6), 1989 August-2004 May (Box 1 (12-Membership), Folder 37)
  - Insurance Department Death Claims - Processed (3 of 6), 1989 August-2004 May (Box 1 (12-Membership), Folder 38)
  - Insurance Department Death Claims - Processed (4 of 6), 1989 August-2004 May (Box 1 (12-Membership), Folder 39)
  - Insurance Department Death Claims - Processed (5 of 6), 1989 August-2004 May (Box 1 (12-Membership), Folder 40)
  - Insurance Department Death Claims - Processed (6 of 6), 1989 August-2004 May (Box 1 (12-Membership), Folder 41)
  - Internal Organizing and Membership Recruitment Materials, 1987; 1989; Undated (Box 1 (12-Membership), Folder 42)
  - Labor History Newsletter, 2010; 2012 (Box 1 (12-Membership), Folder 43)
  - The Labor Dictonary - Activists, Undated (Box 2 (12-Membership), Folder 1)
  - The Legal Department Membership Materials, 2000-2002; 2004-2005 (Box 2 (12-Membership), Folder 2)
  - Local and Unit Officers Manuals, 1980; 1983; 1986; 1989 (Box 2 (12-Membership), Folder 3)
  - Local and Unit Officers Manual, 2001 (Box 2 (12-Membership), Folder 4)
  - Member Resource Guides, 1999-2002 (Box 2 (12-Membership), Folder 5)
  - Membership Applications, 1991; 1997; 2006-2007; 2009 (Box 2 (12-Membership), Folder 6)
  - Membership Flyers and Mailings, 2005; Undated (Box 2 (12-Membership), Folder 7)
  - Memorabilia- Buttons, Undated (Artifact-box 1)
  - Memorabilia- Buttons, Keychain, Undated (Artifact-box 2)
  - Miscellaneous Pamphlets, 1963; 1981-1988; 1991; 1995; 2001 (Box 2 (12-Membership), Folder 8)
  - One Hundredth Anniversary Reflection formAmerican Executiveonline edition, 2010 January (Box 2 (12-Membership), Folder 9)
  - Organize for Power, 2009 (Box 2 (12-Membership), Folder 10)
  - Participants Workbooks, 2007; Undated (Box 2 (12-Membership), Folder 11)
  - Political Action Fund Pension Plan, 2013 (Box 2 (12-Membership), Folder 12)
  - Ralph Distin Politcal Cartoons, Undated (Box 2 (12-Membership), Folder 13)
  - Region Five Membership Materials, 2001-2002; 2005; Undated (Box 2 (12-Membership), Folder 14)
  - Region Four Membership Materials, 2002; 2005 (Box 2 (12-Membership), Folder 15)
  - Region One Membership Materials, 2002; Undated (Box 2 (12-Membership), Folder 16)
  - Region Three Membership Materials, 2002; 2005 (Box 2 (12-Membership), Folder 17)
  - Region Two Membership Materials, 2002 (Box 2 (12-Membership), Folder 18)
  - Resource Manual: CSEA Leap- Yes You Can Workbook, 1998 (Box 2 (12-Membership), Folder 19)
  - Resource Manual: A Civil Service Primer, 2006 (Box 2 (12-Membership), Folder 20)
  - Resource Manual: Civil Service Test Preparation, Undated (Box 2 (12-Membership), Folder 21)
  - Resource Manual: Discipline and Interrogation in the Workplace, 1998 (Box 2 (12-Membership), Folder 22)
  - Resource Manual: Educational Assistance Program, 2005 September 1-2006 August 31 (Box 2 (12-Membership), Folder 23)
  - Resource Manual: Elder Law Handbook, 2005 February (Box 2 (12-Membership), Folder 24)
  - Resource Manual: Ergonomics for Transportation and Trade Workers, 2002 (Box 2 (12-Membership), Folder 25)
  - Resource Manual: Honoring Diversity, Undated (Box 2 (12-Membership), Folder 26)
  - Resource Manual: How to Submit a Resolution and/or Proposal for Constitutional Amendment, 1997 August (Box 2 (12-Membership), Folder 27)
  - Resource Manual: Private SectorResource Manual, 2007 (Box 2 (12-Membership), Folder 28)
  - Resource Manual: Retirement Guide, 2007 (Box 2 (12-Membership), Folder 29)
  - Resource Manual: What to do When the Paychecks Stop, 2005 October (Box 2 (12-Membership), Folder 30)
  - Resource Manual: Working People's History, 2007 (Box 2 (12-Membership), Folder 31)
  - Retired Membership Materials (1 of 5), 1999-2004; 2009-2014; Undated (Box 2 (12-Membership), Folder 32)
  - Retired Membership Materials (2 of 5), 1999-2004; 2009-2014; Undated (Box 2 (12-Membership), Folder 33)
  - Retired Membership Materials (3 of 5), 1999-2004; 2009-2014; Undated (Box 2 (12-Membership), Folder 34)
  - Retired Membership Materials (4 of 5), 1999-2004; 2009-2014; Undated (Box 2 (12-Membership), Folder 35)
  - Retired Membership Materials (5 of 5), 1999-2004; 2009-2014; Undated (Box 2 (12-Membership), Folder 36)
  - The Saftey and Health Department Membership Materials, 1993; 1997; 2002; Undated (Box 2 (12-Membership), Folder 37)
  - Senate and Assembly List, 2012 (Box 2 (12-Membership), Folder 38)
  - Scholarship Booklet, 2004 (Box 2 (12-Membership), Folder 39)
  - Spring Workshops, 2009-2013 (Box 2 (12-Membership), Folder 40)
  - State Government Grievance Workshop, 2007 (Box 2 (12-Membership), Folder 41)
  - Treasurer Report, 1989 March (Box 2 (12-Membership), Folder 42)
  - Women's Conference (1 of 2), 2004 November 19-2004 November 21; Undated (Box 2 (12-Membership), Folder 43)
  - Women's Conference (2 of 2), 2004 November 19-2004 November 21; Undated (Box 2 (12-Membership), Folder 44)